question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The alternative rock band, They Might Be Giants, released their album &#039;Flood&#039; in 1990. ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Animals",
     "question": "A flock of crows is known as a homicide.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "&quot;Undertale&quot; is an RPG created by Toby Fox and released in 2015.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                       "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Deus Ex (2000) does not feature the World Trade Center "
                 "because it was destroyed by terrorist attacks according to the game&#039;s plot.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Politics",
     "question": "Despite being seperated into multiple countries, "
                 "The Scandinavian countries are unified by all having the same monarch.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Gadgets",
     "question": "The communication protocol NFC stands for Near-Field Control.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
                                      "question": "The United States Department "
                                                  "of Homeland Security was"
                                                  " formed in response to the September 11th attacks.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Animals",
     "question": "A bear does NOT defecate during hibernation. ", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Computers",
                                       "question": "Linus Torvalds created Linux and Git.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                       "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
